[narrator] Once upon a time,
in an office building far, far, away,
a seemingly insignificant business meeting was called...
- [Boss]  I'm very glad you
all have gathered here.
- If I may ask...
why are we here today?
- You shouldn't ask the boss
questions like that.
You know how she gets.
- Actually that's a good question.
I mean what's the point, really?
Every week we sit around and gaba gaba--
- Hey!
Don't you think you're being
a little disrespectful?
- Who asked you?
- [Zeus] I asked her.
- [Boss] Ahh, Zeus!
Greek deity of the sky!
I'm glad you could join us.
- Hey Boss...
What's uh, Zeus, doing at this meeting?
- And how do we know that's Zeus talking?
- Yeah, how do we know that's really Zeus?
- How the [bleep] do I know
that's [bleep] Zeus?
I'll [bleep] tell you how...
ask him to prove it.
- How are you going to get the
Greek deity of the sky
to prove he's the Greek deity of the sky?
This is the king of Mount
Olympus speaking to us
from goodness knows where...
You can't go around questioning the
authenticity of Greek deities!
You know,
they tend to get
really ticked off!
- [Zeus] I know how I can prove it.
I'll tell you what color
you're thinking of.
Okay, thinking of one?
Okay...
...now...
Tell me what it is!
- Yellow.
- Blue!
- He was asking me!
- I am pretty sure he was asking me!
- [Boss] Can we please get
back to our meeting?
- Sorry.
- [Boss] The thing is...
I've been hearing,
you know,
the way that someone
HEARS about things...
I hear SOME people around here were...
[thunder]
- [Zeus] Oops!
Excuse me!
- Wowie zowie, that stinks!
- I didn't think thunder had a smell.
- [speaking Spanish]
- Dude! I think I might pass out!
- ♪ [mumbling a song] ♪
- [Boss] What was that?
- Oh, it's just a little something I sing
to myself when I don't feel so good.
- Ooh! I love songs!
What is it?
- ♪ [singing a Woody Guthrie song] ♪
- ♪ [singing] ♪
- ♪ [all singing together] ♪
- ♪ [Zeus singing] ♪
- You skipped a line!
- [Zeus] What?
- Nothing.
- How does Zeus know Woody Guthrie?
- [all] Shhh!
- [Boss] Dismissed!
- [all] Yay!