Comfortably get back into the rhythm again,
heart rate was peaking up at 170.
I'm gutted.
Absolutely gutted.
Got it back in my legs to get
to the top but, snow's in the way.
Just want to go and have a look.
Just round that corner and if there's tarmac...
This is nuts! Just that corner there,
I carry the bike through to there and I'm off.
What?
No, I need to get up round here. Anyone?
12 metres high mate,
we've gotta go back.
What the snow?
Yeah. We cant go on.
He's saying you could die mate,
we've gotta go.
Thank you.
Yesterday, after we got snowed out
of Madeleine, ah, I was absolutely gutted.
My legs would've got me up there,
but Madeleine said no.
I had a bit of a brief this morning,
as to what's to come...
So today we've got another legendary
Tour de France climb for you to take on,
the Col de la Croix de Fer
which is the "Call of the Iron Cross".
It was first used in the tour in 1947.
So they've been coming up
here for over 50 years.
The last 5 or 6k's from what I hear
is gonna smash my legs to pieces.
I'm gunning for this one.
I need this one in the bag.
[Music]
There you go buddy.
Thank you.
[Music plays again]
Just find a good rhythm.
Yeah.
Find a good rhythm, tap it out.
Feel the rhythm! Feel the rhythm!
[laughs]
Ahh, I've got no pacing left.
You can do it.
Dig, dig, dig, dig!
Oh (breathes heavily).
This is not your lungs,
it's your legs just exploding.
We're coming into cloud land now.
[Puffing] Oh! My ears popped. Jeez.
You get the impression
they do not want you at the top.
[radio static]
...you're about 100 metres away.
Oh, hands are like ice blocks!
Feet, can't even feel my toes. Oh.
Oh my legs!
Can't even hold a straight line.
It's such a long day out,
but, this, don't even know now,
how much further you've got to go
'cos you can't see in front of you.
[Applause and cheering]
We're getting there are we there?
Are we there?
[Car beeps horn]
Yes!
[Cheering continues]
Yeah! How's that!
Ollie! Ollie! Ollie! Let three line ends here